[
  {
    "question": "Standard 9-1-1 line greeting:",
    "answer": "Orange County 9-1-1, what is the address of your emergency? (Repeat, unless it matches ALI.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the 2nd question in the 9-1-1 call process?",
    "answer": "What's the phone number you are calling from? (Repeat, unless it matches ANI. Say VERIFIED if it matches.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the 3rd question in the 9-1-1 call process?",
    "answer": "What's your name?"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the 4th question in the 9-1-1 call process?",
    "answer": "Okay, tell me exactly what happened."
  },
  {
    "question": "Who can you use the Aspirin tool on?",
    "answer": "Patient is functionally alert, 16 years of age or older, no reported stroke symptoms, and not pregnant."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the 5 W's?",
    "answer": "WHERE, WHEN, WHAT, WHO, WEAPONS"
  },
  {
    "question": "Standard alarm / non-emergency / administrative line greeting:",
    "answer": "Orange County Communications, this is [... YOUR NAME ...]"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a DOMESTIC?",
    "answer": "Man made structure e.g., pool, hot tub, bathtub"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a SPECIALIZED?",
    "answer": "Natural setting or man-made structure not intended for domestic use e.g., lake, river, canal, water tank."
  },
  {
    "question": "When would you use the active assailant protocol vs the shooting / stabbing protocol.",
    "answer": "When the assailant has unrestricted access to victims."
  },
  {
    "question": "What protocol would you use when a vehicle is on fire in a free standing garage?",
    "answer": "Vehicle fire."
  },
  {
    "question": "What protocol would you use when a vehicle is on fire in a home garage, or garage attached to a building?",
    "answer": "Structure fire."
  },
  {
    "question": "What protocol should a barking dog be handled on?",
    "answer": "Protocol 105 - Animal."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is considered 'multiple patients' for a medical event?",
    "answer": "3 or more patients."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you do when a call for service is requested (CFS)?",
    "answer": "Select 'New Event' from CAD."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the 9-1-1 call answering rules?",
    "answer": "9-1-1 lines will be answered first before any other line, will be answered within 3 rings, and calltakers will refrain from putting the call on hold until enough pertinent info has been obtained."
  },
  {
    "question": "How are the different MVC (motor vehicle colision) nature codes used?",
    "answer": "When patient with injury present, use the EMD MVCPI nature code. When no injury, use the EPD MVCLE. When hazardous materials reported, also include the EFD MVCFI."
  },
  {
    "question": "Priority Symptoms",
    "answer": "Abnormal breathing | Chest pain / discomfort (any) | Decreased level of consciousness | Serious hemorrhage."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the EPD disconnect?",
    "answer": "Urgent dissconect."
  }
]
